A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1957
  - American Association, 1957 (Reel C-1207)
  - American Bar Association, 1957 (Reel C-1207)
  - American Committee, 1957 (Reel C-1207)
  - American Council on Education, 1957 (Reel C-1207)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Council…, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Educational Theatre Association, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Friends Service Committee, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Political Science association, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Society of Agricultural Engineers, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Society of Public Administration, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American Society... [General], 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - American... [General], 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Area I (Peace), 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Area IV (Education), 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Arizona, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Armstrong…, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Army, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Arnold, Edwin G., 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Art (Organizations), 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Arts, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Armour Research Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Armour Research Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Ascher, Charles S., 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Asia, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Asia Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1208)
  - Asia Society, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Associated…, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Association for Asian Studies, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Association (General), 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Athens College (Greece), 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Ayub, S.M., 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bacon, G.H., 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bailey, George, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Baker, John C., 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Barnes, Naomi, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Barton…, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Baumgartner, Leona, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bazelon, David, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Beale, Neville, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Beck, Elizabeth, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Benton, William, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Berger…, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bernays, Edward, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Black, James, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Board of Higher Education, Disciples of Christ, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Boston… [Organizations], 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Bradley, Omar, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - British…, 1957 (Reel C-1209)
  - Brookings Institution, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Brooklyn Veterans Administration Hospital, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Brown, Courtney, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Brownlee, James, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Bryant, William Cullen, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Bureau…, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Burma, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - Burns, Leslie, 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - CA – CZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - California, University of (Berkeley), 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - California, University of (Los Angeles), 1957 (Reel C-1210)
  - California… [General], 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Cambridge, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Cameron…, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Camp…, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Canadian… [Organizations], 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Carnegie… [General], 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Carroll, John J., 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Catholic … [General], 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Central University of Venezuela, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Chicago, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Children's…, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - China, 1957 (Reel C-1211)
  - Cole, Albert M., 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Colorado State Planning Division, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Columbia University, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Columbia…, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Commission…, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Conference…, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Conference of Foundations, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Conference of Southwest Foundations, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Conference of the American High School, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Conference on Asian Affairs, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Connecticut General Life Insurance Co., 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Cook…, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Cooper, John C., 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Cornell University, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Council…, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Council for the Advancement of Small Colleges, 1957 (Reel C-1212)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Cox…, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - DA – DZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Das Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - David, Donald K., 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Davis…, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Dayton Daily News, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Detroit Times, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Douglas, Mrs. William A, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Doyle, Clyde, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Dunwoody Industrial Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - EA – EZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - East Orange General Hospital, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Economic Club of Detroit, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Edwards, Fred P., 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Encyclopedia…, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Ensminger, Douglas, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Eureka College, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Europe, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - European Productivity Agency, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Evans, Mrs. Edmund C, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Exchange of Persons, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - FA – FZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Farley, Hugh, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Fisher, Alan, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Ford…, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Franklin, George, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Free Europe Committee, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Free Europe Press, 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - Fund for Adult Education (FAE), 1957 (Reel C-1213)
  - GA – GZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Gaither, H. Rowan, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Gant, George F., 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Gould…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Goucher College, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Goldman…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Goodhousekeeping, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Gordon…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Governmental Affairs institute, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Graham…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Greene…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - HA – HZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hale…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hall…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hanson…, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harmel, Pierre, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harris, Michael S., 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harris, Seymour E., 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harris, Seymour E. – Attachments, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harris… (General), 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harrison, Anna, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Harvard University, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Heald, Henry T., 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hilsman, Roger, 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - Hobson, Jesse E., 1957 (Reel C-1214)
  - House…, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - IA – IZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Illinois, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Illinois, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Imperial…, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - India, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - India... (Organizations), 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Indian... (Organizations), 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Indiana University, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Indiana, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Industrial…, 1957 (Reel C-1215)
  - Indonesia, 1957 (Reel C-1216)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, 1957 (Reel C-1216)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1957 (Reel C-1216)
  - Institute of International Education, 1957 (Reel C-1216)
  - Institute… [General], 1957 (Reel C-1216)
  - Inter-… [General], 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Center for Regional Planning and Development, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Commission of Jurists, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Legal Studies, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Press Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International Training and Research (ITR), 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - International (General), 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - Iowa, 1957 (Reel C-1217)
  - Iowa State University, 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - Iran, 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - Iraq, 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - Italy, 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) Fellowships, 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - Iverson, Kenneth R., 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - JA – JZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1218)
  - Jackson Committee, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jackson…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jacobs…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jacoby, Neil H., 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jaffe, A.J., 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jannuzi, F. Tomasson, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Japan, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jasney, Naum, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jenkins…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jenny, Hans H., 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jerg, M. (Mrs.), 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jewish… [Organizations], 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Johnson…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Johnston…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Joint Commission on Mental Illness and Health, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jones…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jordan, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Joyce, Jean, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Jump Memorial Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Junior…, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1957 (Reel C-1219)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: KA – Krek, 1957 (Reel C-1220)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: Krek – KZ, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kahn…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kansas… [Organizations], 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kaplan…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Keio University, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kelly…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kennedy…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kentucky, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Kerr, Clark, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Khan…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - King…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - Knapp…, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: LA – Lewanski, 1957 (Reel C-1221)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: Li – LZ, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lane…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Larsen, Roy E., 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Larson…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Laszlo…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - League…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Leahy…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lee…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lehmann…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Leis…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lerner…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lever…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Levin…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Levine…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Levy…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lewis…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Library of Congress…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lincoln…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lind…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Lindsay…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Little…, 1957 (Reel C-1222)
  - Livney, Martin, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Lockley, Lawrence C., 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Logan…, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - London, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Long…, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Los Angeles, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Louisville, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - Lowe…, 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - McA – McZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1223)
  - McKenzie…, 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - McKinsey and Company, Inc, 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - McDaniel, Joseph M. Jr., 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - MacDonald, Keith A., 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - MacDowell Association Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - McHenry, Dean E., 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: MA – Mercy College, Detroit, 1957 (Reel C-1224)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: Meredith Publishing – MZ, 1957 (Reel C-1225)
  - Malone…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mann…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mannes College of Music, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Marks…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Marshall…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Martens, Sten, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Martin…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Maryland, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mason…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Massachusetts, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Maury…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Maximlite Schools, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - May…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mayer…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mayer, Peter, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mayo…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Mead…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Medical, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Memphis, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Merchant…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Merrill…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Methodist…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Metropolitan, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Meyer…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Miami, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Miami, University of (Florida), 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Michigan, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Michigan State University, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Michigan, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Midburg Council Study, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Middle…, 1957 (Reel C-1226)
  - Midwest…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Midwestern Universalities Research Association, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Miller…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Mills…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Ministry of higher Education (Poland), 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Ministry of Welfare (Nigeria), 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Minnesota, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Missouri Division of Resources and Development, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Mitchell…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Mitchell Camera of New York, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Montana, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Moore…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Mooresville, Town of (North Carolina), 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Moran…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morehouse College, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morgan…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morris…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morrison…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morse…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Morton…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Moser…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Mount…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Murphy…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Murray…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - Museum…, 1957 (Reel C-1227)
  - NA –NZ {General File], 1957 (Reel C-1228)
  - National…, 1957 (Reel C-1228)
  - National Association…, 1957 (Reel C-1228)
  - National Broadcasting Company Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1228)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1228)
  - National Catholic…, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Committee…, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Committee on Community Foundations, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Council…, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Education Association, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Health Council, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Information Bureau, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Military-Industrial Conference, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Municipal League, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Planning Association, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Recreation Association, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - National Science Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - Naval War College, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - Near East…, 1957 (Reel C-1229)
  - Near East Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Nebraska…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Nelson…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Nepal, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New England Hospital Assembly, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New York…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New York, College of the City of, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, Syracuse, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - New York University, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - North…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - North Carolina, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - North Dakota, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Northern…, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Northwestern University, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - OA – OZ [General File]: OA – Ohkawa, Kazushi, 1957 (Reel C-1230)
  - OA – OZ [General File]: Ohkawa, Kazushi – OZ, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Oak…, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Office of Education, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Office of Intelligence Research, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Ohio State University, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Ohkawa, Kazushi, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Old…, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Operations Mission to…, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Organization for European Economic Cooperation, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Osteopathic Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Overseas…, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Overseas Development, 1957 (Reel C-1231)
  - Overseas Development Program Standard Reports, 1957 (Reel C-1232)
  - Overseas Development Program Status Reports, 1957 (Reel C-1232)
  - Overseas Representatives Conference, 1957 (Reel C-1232)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: PA – Pepperdine College, 1957 (Reel C-1232)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: Peranio – PZ, 1957 (Reel C-1233)
  - Pacific, 1957 (Reel C-1233)
  - Palmer…, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pakistan, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Parker…, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pan American, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pearson…, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - People to People Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Perkins…, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Peterson…, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Philadelphia, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Philippines, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pierce College, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pierson, Frank C., 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Polish, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Porter, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Portland, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Poynter, Nelson, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Presidents Committee for Education Beyond the High School, 1957 (Reel C-1234)
  - Press Intelligence, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - Princeton University, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - Public Revenue Education Council, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - Public…, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - Puerto Rico, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - QA – QZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - Quint, Malcolm, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: RA – Robb, 1957 (Reel C-1235)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: Robb – RZ, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Rabinowitz, Richard W., 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Radio Free Europe, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Rand Corporation, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Rao…, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Rasmussen, Ann, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Read, Margaret, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Real Estate, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Reed…, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Research (General), 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Research Society for Creative Altruism, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Resources for the Future, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Retina Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1236)
  - Rhodes…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rice…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Richardson…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Riker, Wiliam H., 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Roberts…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Robins, Seymour, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Robinson…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rochester... [General], 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rogers…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Roosevelt…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rudlin, Walter A., 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Russel…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Russian Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - Rutgers…, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: SA – Schenectady, 1957 (Reel C-1237)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Schenectady – Soane, 1957 (Reel C-1238)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Soane – SZ, 1957 (Reel C-1239)
  - Saint…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Saint John…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Saint Joseph…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Saint Mary's…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Saint Mary's College (Notre Dame), 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Salveson, M.E., 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - San…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Sapir, Michael, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Sastri, Sakuntala Rao, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Save the Children Federation, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Schmidt…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - School…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - School of Advanced International Studies, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Schoor, Deena, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Schultz…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Schwartz…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Scott…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Seattle, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Second…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Senate, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Shinner Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Silvett, A.N. (LCDR), 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Simon…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Simpson…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Singer…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Sister's…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Skinner…, 1957 (Reel C-1240)
  - Smith…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Smith, Bruce Lannes, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Smith, Lloyd F., 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Smythe…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Snyder…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Society…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Soewand…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Soloman…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Sookmyung, Women's University, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - South…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Southern…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Southern California, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Southwestern…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Spafford Research Corporation, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Spartanburg county Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Spencer…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Springarn, Stephen J, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Springfield College, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Stanford University, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - State…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - State Department (United States), 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - State University of New York, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Stern…, 1957 (Reel C-1241)
  - Stevens…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Stewart…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Stone…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Stout…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Student…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Studentowicz, Kazimierz, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Sullivan…, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Swayzee, Cleon O., 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Syracuse University, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Syria, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - Szilard, Leo, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - TA – TZ [General File]: TA – Today's Art, 1957 (Reel C-1242)
  - TA – TZ [General File]: Today's Art – TZ, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Tata Iron and Steel Co., 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Taylor…, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Teacher, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Technion-Israel Institute of Technology, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Temple University, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Tennessee, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Texas…, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Texas Agricultural and Mechanical College System, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Texas Personnel and Management Association, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Texas, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Thayer…, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Thomas…, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Thompson…, 1957 (Reel C-1243)
  - Thurber, Clarence E., 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Toledo…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tolin, Ole E., 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tri-State Hospital Assembly, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Trinity…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tufts University, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tuition Plan Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tulane University, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tunisia, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Turkey, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Turner…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Tyler…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - UA – UZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - UNESCO, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - UNESCO…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Union Research Institute, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - Union…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - United College, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - United Community Funds and Councils of America, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - United Nations…, 1957 (Reel C-1244)
  - United States Information Agency, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - United States…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - United States Military Academy, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - United…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - University College…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - University…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Urwick, Lyndall F., 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Utah…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - VA – VZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Van…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Vanderbilt…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1957 (Reel C-1245)